{"allRoundData":[
{"name":"Math","timeLimitInSeconds":20,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":20,
"questions": [{"questionText":"6+2","answers":[{"answerText":"7","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"8","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"12+4","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"16","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"18","isCorrect":false}]},
{"questionText":"10+13","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"23","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"18","isCorrect":false}]}]},

{"name":"Subtraction","timeLimitInSeconds":20,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":20,
"questions":[{"questionText":"6-2","answers":[{"answerText":"7","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"12-4","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"16","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"8","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"10-5","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"18","isCorrect":false}]}]},

{"name":"Math","timeLimitInSeconds":20,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":20,
"questions":[{"questionText":"What number is in the ones place: 45","answers":[{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"What number is in the hundreds place: 323","answers":[{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"What number is in the tens place: 32389","answers":[{"answerText":"8","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":false}]}]},

{"name":"Math","timeLimitInSeconds":20,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":20,
"questions": [{"questionText":"3+2","answers":[{"answerText":"7","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"4+1","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"18","isCorrect":false}]},
{"questionText":"10+3","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"13","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"18","isCorrect":false}]}]},

{"name":"Subtraction","timeLimitInSeconds":20,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":20,
"questions":[{"questionText":"4-1","answers":[{"answerText":"7","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"10-4","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"16","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"6","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"1-1","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"18","isCorrect":false}]}]},

{"name":"Math","timeLimitInSeconds":20,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":20,
"questions":[{"questionText":"What number is in the ones place: 67","answers":[{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"7","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"What number is in the hundreds place: 400","answers":[{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"What number is in the tens place: 23","answers":[{"answerText":"8","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":false}]}]},

{"name":"Math","timeLimitInSeconds":20,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":20,
"questions": [{"questionText":"10+4","answers":[{"answerText":"7","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"14","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"11+3","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"14","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"18","isCorrect":false}]},
{"questionText":"10+1","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"11","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"18","isCorrect":false}]}]},

{"name":"Subtraction","timeLimitInSeconds":20,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":20,
"questions":[{"questionText":"7-4","answers":[{"answerText":"7","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"1-0","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"16","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"4-2","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"18","isCorrect":false}]}]},

{"name":"Math","timeLimitInSeconds":20,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":20,
"questions":[{"questionText":"What number is in the ones place: 38","answers":[{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"8","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"What number is in the hundreds place: 475","answers":[{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"What number is in the tens place: 385","answers":[{"answerText":"8","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":false}]}]},

{"name":"Math","timeLimitInSeconds":20,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":20,
"questions": [{"questionText":"4+9","answers":[{"answerText":"7","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"13","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"12+1","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"13","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"18","isCorrect":false}]},
{"questionText":"7+3","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"18","isCorrect":false}]}]},

{"name":"Subtraction","timeLimitInSeconds":20,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":20,
"questions":[{"questionText":"6-1","answers":[{"answerText":"7","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"4-1","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"16","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"8-3","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"18","isCorrect":false}]}]},

{"name":"Math","timeLimitInSeconds":20,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":20,
"questions":[{"questionText":"What number is in the ones place: 22","answers":[{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"What number is in the hundreds place: 867","answers":[{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"8","isCorrect":true}]},
{"questionText":"What number is in the tens place: 10","answers":[{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":false}]}]}

]}